Thomas Wiltshire

Hello, my name is Thomas. I'm a hard-working, passionate programmer that is currently living in Ferntree Gully, Victoria, Australia. Over the last 3 years, I have been studying at the Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE) to obtain a Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds (Programming).

Location: Unit 3 / 4 Dorset Road, Ferntree Gully VIC 3156

Contacts: +61 466661042 thomas.wiltshire14@icloud.com

Portfolio: thomaswiltshire.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds, Academy of Interactive Entertainment — *Melbourne*, *Victoria*

January 2017 - December 2019

Certificate III in Multimedia, Kyabram Community and Learning Centre — *Kyabram*, *Victoria*

January 2013 - December 2014

Primary School / High School, Kyabram P-12 College / Kyabram St Augustine's College — *Kyabram, Victoria*

January 2002 - December 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Trainee, Advance Computing — *Kyabram*, *Victoria*

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 Year)

While at Advance Computing, I started a Certificate 3 in Information Technology as a part of my traineeship in software development. I mainly worked in software, with some helpdesk and support responsibilities.

Crew Member, Mc Donald's Australia — *Echuca*, *Victoria*

March 2015 - January 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at McDonald's within the kitchen. I gained irreplaceable skills in teamwork, punctuality, leadership, cooking and cleaning.

IT Technicians Assistant (Work Placement), Kyabram Community and Learning Centre — *Kyabram, Victoria*

March 2014 - December 2014 (1/2 Year)

I worked at KCLC, as a part of my VCAL studies, in the IT department, helping with various repair jobs, network issues and computer assistance.

NOTABLE PROJECTS (FOUND AT THOMASWILTSHIRE.COM)

Lua C++ Bindings Project, Technical Design Document (Developed for the Gypsy's Tale Project) and Zombie Game (A Passion Project).

EXPERIENCE AND SKILLS

Languages: C# (3 years), C++ (3 years), Lua (3 years), HTML5/CSS (1 ½ year), Javascript (½ year).

Software: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, MonoDevelop, SVN, Git, Github, SourceTree.

Hardware: Development Lifecycles of iOS, Android, Windows and Macintosh.

Frameworks: Unity (2 years), Love2D (2 years), WinForms (1 year), UWP (1 year), UE4 (<1/2 year).

Management: Formal education in project management (Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Waterfall), Documentation and UML.

Other: Great Teamwork and Troubleshooting Skills.

REFERENCES

THIS IS A PUBLIC LOCATION/WEBSITE!

IN ORDER TO PROTECT REFERENCE INFORMATION YOU WILL BE REQUIRED TO PLEASE CONTACT ME TO REQUEST REFERENCE INFORMATION.